infoatoms.com 2013-09-02

# InfoAtoms | Privacy Policy

### Last Updated: November 11, 2012

## INTRODUCTION

InfoAtoms, Inc. ("Company, "we" or "us") is the distributor of the InfoAtoms plugin ("Plugin" or "InfoAtoms") which is available at www.infoatoms.com (the "Site"). InfoAtoms allows users to view definitions, translations and search results without leaving the page by just highlighting keywords or phrases. The Plugin, Site, and any related features, products, services, functionalities or content offered by the Company shall be referred to herein as "Services". Use of the Services is governed by the [InfoAtoms Terms of Service](https://www.infoatoms.com/terms-of-service), and this Privacy Policy (together the Terms of Service and Privacy Policy for the "Agreement"). Company and Services are based in the U.S. You must be 18 or over to use the Services. 

This Privacy Policy applies to all users of Services, including InfoAtoms and the Site. This Privacy Policy explains the type of information the Company collects, how the information is used, with who the information is shared, and extent to which the information can be associated with a particular user. Types of information may include Personally Identifiable Information ("PII") - such as email or name when submitting a customer service request - and Non- Personally Identifiable Information - such as IP Address and Browser. In some cases, information collected by the Plugin may be used or shared with third parties for the purposes of displaying targeted advertisements to you. InfoAtoms does not attempt to analyze web usage data the individual identity of any plugin user. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS POLICY OR THE AGREEMENT IN ITS ENTIRETY, YOU SHOULD NOT USE THE INFOATOMS SERVICES OR SITE. IF YOU ARE CURRENTLY A USER AND DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS POLICY OR THE AGREEMNT IN ITS ENTIRETY, YOU SHOULD UNINSTALL IMMEDIATELY (See the Uninstall Instructions). 

InfoAtoms is ad-supported. During general internet usage on sites where InfoAtoms operates, users may see additional banner, search, pop-up, pop-under, and in-text link advertisements. These advertisements will be identified with the InfoAtoms Name or Logo. InfoAtoms and all related advertisements are not affiliated with or endorsed by any underlying websites. 

## COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

### WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED?

#### USER SUBMITTED INFORMATION

When contacting InfoAtoms for issues related to the Service, Users have the option but not the requirement to submit personal information. The personal information (such as email address, name, and other identifying information) is collected to enable InfoAtoms to respond to issues and communicate effectively. However, the submission of personal information is not required but response cannot be guaranteed if a mechanism of communication is not provided.

#### COLLECTED INFORMATION

Non-personally identifiable information, such as IP Address, unique identifier number, operating system, browser, search queries, and browsing history is collected during normal use of the Service. The non-personally identifiable information is stored and used to further the performance of InfoAtoms such as maintaining and improving the Services and displaying more relevant advertisements. The information may be combined with information from third parties. InfoAtoms shares non-personally identifiable information (including search and URL history) to advertising partners to improve product performance and ad relevance.

### HOW IS THE COLLECTED INFORMATION COLLECTED?

#### TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES

The company uses browser cookies, storage data, JavaScript, web beacons, pixels, flash cookies, and other tracking technologies to collect non-personally identifiable information. The tracking technologies collect and pass the collected information with an anonymous unique identifier. The collected information may include,but without limitation, search queries, browsing history, browser type and other performance data in order to improve the performance of the Services and improve marketing including, but without limitation, more relevant ads and to conduct market research. The company may also use cookies and similar tools to relate your use of the Services to personal information obtained from you or a reputable third party.

#### THIRD PARTY COLLECTION

Third parties may also use cookies and other tracking technologies described, but not limited to, above to collect similar usage information. The Company does not control these third parties and their use of these technologies is governed by the privacy policies of the third parties using such technologies. For more information about third part ad networks that use these technologies, see [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/). Most internet browsers are by default set to accept cookies. The settings for these cookies can be updated or set to block cookies altogether. To change your cookie settings please see the "help" guide of your particular internet browser for more information. To change the settings of Flash technologies, such as cookies, see the Flash Management Tool on Adobe's website. By changing certain cookie and other tracking technology setting the Services may not perform as intended. 

#### CHILDREN UNDER 18

The Company, and Services are neither intended for, nor directed to, persons under the age of 18. If InfoAtoms learns that a User or someone with access to InfoAtoms is under the age of 18, InfoAtoms will terminate the use of the Service for the User and delete any related information.

### HOW IS THE INFORMATION USED?

The collected information will be used in one of the following, but not limited to, ways:

#### PROVIDE AND MANAGE SERVICES

The information collected is used to provide you with Services. In addition, the information is used to improve and optimize those services by delivering relevant content and advertising, and to provide you with customer support. We may use aggregated or anonymous data about use of an activity on the Services to assist us in this regard and such data is not subject to this Privacy Policy.

#### ALLOW THIRD PARTY SESRVICE PROVIDERS TO ASSIST US IN PROVIDING AND MANAGING SERVICES

The Company may make your non-public personal information available to certain third party companies, contractors and individuals to perform functions. Examples include, but are not limited to, storing and analyzing data, providing search results and links (including paid listings), hosting and providing customer service. These third party service providers have access to user information needed to perform their functions, but are required to protect non-public personal informational provided to them and not use it for any other purpose than for the service they are providing to the company.

#### CONTACT YOU

The Company may contact you in response to your inquiries from the support page or other means of correspondence you have utilized. We will use any personal information you voluntarily provide to us solely for the purpose of responding to your inquiry.

#### DELIVER RELEVANT ADVERTISING

The information provided to us, and the collected information during your use of the Site or Service through the use of cookies and other technologies, may be used to assist us in delivering you relevant ads when you use the Services. We may share anonymous, non-personally identifiable, or aggregated information with third parties, with whom we work who help us deliver ads, to improve the relevancy of ads when using the Service. These third party advertising networks and advertisers may use cookies and similar technologies to collect and track non-personally identifiable information such as demographic information, aggregated information, and internet activity to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interest. The type of information collected by each partner varies. The information practices of these Ad Companies are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. If you would prefer not to participate in the services offered through these solutions, you can always opt-out of this activity for certain partners by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

#### PROTECT THE RIGHTS OF COMPANY AND OUR USERS

In certain instances , the Company may disclose user information without providing notice or choice where the Company has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: (i) protect or defend the legal right or property of the Company, our affiliated companies or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (ii) protect the safety and security of users of the Services or members of the public; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or (iv) comply with the lay or legal process.

#### COMPLETE A MERGER OR SALE OF ASSETS

If the company sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, the Company may transfer our information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

### NOTICE AND MODIFICATIONS

#### MEANS OF NOTICE AND PRIVACY POLICY MODIFICATIONS

The Company may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to InfoAtoms information practices. If the Company makes any material changes, this Privacy Policy is the means by which the Company provides you with notice about its collection and use of personal information. The company may modify this Privacy Policy at any time, and each such modification will be effective upon notice to you, including posting on the Site. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. You are responsible for periodically check the Privacy Policy for material changes. You may also receive a copy of this Privacy Policy by emailing us at [support@infoatoms.com](mailto:support@infoatoms.com). You agree that your continued use of the service following the posting of any changes to this Privacy Policy and after the changes take effect will constitute your acceptance of such changes. If you do not agree to future changes to this Privacy Policy, stop using the Service after the effective date of such changes and uninstall the Plugin.

#### LOCATION OF DATA

The Services are hosted in the United States. If you are a user located outside the U.S., you understand and consent to having any personal information you provide transferred to, processed, and stored in the U.S. and other countries where data protection and other privacy laws may not offer the same level of protection as in your jurisdiction, such as the European Union, This includes the use of cookies and other tracking technologies as described above.

#### ADVERTISED OR LINKED SERVICES

The Services may be linked to or advertise third party sites or services, including online stores, rewards programs, trial offers, newsletters, contests or sweepstakes. The Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of any such third parties, and once you leave the Services via a link or click on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party service or site.

### SECURITY

The Company follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to the Company, both during transmission and once received. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security

#### USER CONTROL AND UNINSTALLING SOFTWARE

InfoAtoms may be uninstalled at anytime by following the instructions on the support page. After you uninstall InfoAtoms, certain related files may remain on your system. These remnant files are record of your previous download of the Company's software and are not executable programs. These files help the Company to prevent fraud on the Services and better service you.

#### CONTACT US

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, InfoAtoms and/or if you would like access to update or delete your personal information please contact us below:

InfoAtoms, Inc.  
5580 La Jolla Bld. 511  
La Jolla, CA 92037  

#### CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request please use the contact information above.
